<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Turismo Yarumal</string>

    <string name="mayarinoDescripcion">It is a bridge located near the Mayan farm over the river called Brisas del Nechi, excellent to spend an afternoon with the family</string>

    <string name="parqueDescripcion">
        It is the main park located near all the local commerce of the town such as restaurants, small shopping centers and the basilica La Merced
    </string>

    <string name="preventorioDescripcion">
        It is a place where there are various spaces available for sports such as basketball soccer fields, motocross track, downhill as well as a medium pool.
    </string>

    <string name="coliseoDescipcion">
        It is a space ready for sports where you can find a court that can be used for football and basketball, a skating rink,
        a large pool, tennis court and gym
    </string>

    <string name="panoramaDescripcion">
        Hotel Open 24 hours, We are located in the main park with excellent views to the east, we also offer private parking service for motorcycles
    </string>

    <string name="armoniaDescripcion">
        If you are looking for a quiet place to rest and that is away from the hustle and bustle; the Armonía hotel is your best option.
        We are located diagonally to the new transport terminal of the municipality and close to the hospital.
        We have rooms for 1 person, couple or family. Each room has a private bathroom, hot water, digital television and internet.
    </string>

    <string name="amajariDescripcion">
        We have the best service at your disposal, rooms with breakfast included
        It has at your service comfortable rooms with private bathroom, hot water, color TV, WiFi (FREE),
        If you want to share a special night with your partner, we have the best option
    </string>

    <string name="granDescripcion">
        We have at your disposal excellent and comfortable facilities, very good service and low prices.
        Located in the center of the city two blocks from the central park with cheap parking spaces
        close to the hotel and good restaurants around
    </string>

    <string name="relaxDescripcion">
        We are located in the transport terminal, we have comfortable rooms, gym, Turkish bath and synthetic court
    </string>

    <string name="opcion1">English</string>
    <string name="opcion2">Spanish</string>
    <string name="opcion3">About..</string>

    <string-array name="LugaresInteres">
        <item>Hotel</item>
        <item>Interes</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="ver_mas">+ View More</string>
    <string name="lugarHotel">Hotel</string>
    <string name="lugarInteres">Places of interest</string>
    <string name="nombre_lugar">Name of place</string>
    <string name="descripcion_lugar">Description of the place</string>
    <string name="contacto_lugar">Contact of the place</string>
    <string name="direccion_lugar">Direction of the place</string>
    <string name="contribute">Contribute a place</string>
    <string name="tipo_lugar">Type of place</string>
    <string name="guardar_lugar">Save place</string>
    <string name="about">This is an application created purely for educational purposes</string>

    <string name="subido">Your place will be reviewed to evaluate if it is suitable or not</string>
    <string name="subir_error">An error has occurred and your place could not be uploaded</string>
    <string name="obtener_error">You must fill in the name, address, description fields and select an image</string>
</resources>